<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Our Projects on ii</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Our Projects on ii</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>APISnoop</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/apisnoop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/apisnoop/</guid>
      <description>APISnoop is a site that tracks the progress of the Kubernetes conformance project by analysing the audit logs from end-to-end test runs, to see how many conformant endpoints are hit by conformance tests. Our team used postgres and svelte to build APISnoop, and the site is used by the larger Kubernetes community to set priorities for conformance work and reduce the creation of technical debt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coop Mode</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/ublue/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/ublue/</guid>
      <description> Cloud based solution to help people be in the same space, on the same page. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Educational Outreach</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/education/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/education/</guid>
      <description>In collaboration with select education providers and youth programs, we curate custom workshops, programmes and bootcamps to spark curiosity and foster interest in open source.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Events</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/events/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/events/</guid>
      <description>ii regularly runs, supports or participates in events across the globe to promote opportunities in Open Source - career expos, conferences, Meetups, information sessions and industry site tours to name a few!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes Conformance</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/k8s-conformance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/k8s-conformance/</guid>
      <description>We work with the CNCF to help ensure consistent features for Kubernetes across vendor offerings and open source implementations. Our work includes tracking conformance progress with audit log analysis, gitops bots that verify conformance submissions, writing tests to increase conformance coverage, and release-informing bots that help ensure no new Kubernetes endpoints are added without tests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes Infra</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/kubernetes-infra/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/kubernetes-infra/</guid>
      <description>Our team works regularly with the Kubernetes infra working group, to help distribute the infrastructural load of the Kubernetes project across multiple community providers to help ensure the long-term sustainability of Kubernetes development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mentoring</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/mentoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/mentoring/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;#39;re passionate about empowering the next generation of technologists, servant and community leaders, innovators and disruptors through dedicated mentoring.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resource Development</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/resource-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/resource-development/</guid>
      <description>&amp;#34;The right tools are the bridge between curiosity and knowledge.&amp;#34; (Anon), which is why ii designs a range of learning tools and strategies to help make sense of the world of tech!</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
